<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Announcements on Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/announcements/</link><description>Recent content in Announcements on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/announcements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advisory: Response to transactions being automatically retried</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/announcements/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/announcements/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</guid><description>Binance has today paused Dogecoin withdrawals and stated they have found a &amp;ldquo;major issue&amp;rdquo; in Doecoin. We wanted to address this:
Several months ago (noting while an earlier post stated a year, first confirmed mention is April) Binance notified us they had cases where transactions were stuck, meaning they were not being mined successfully. We suggested Binance use RBF (replace by fee) on these transactions, which would replace the original transactions with a new transaction with a higher fee paid.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Binance has today paused Dogecoin withdrawals and stated they have found a &ldquo;major issue&rdquo; in Doecoin. We wanted to address this:</p>
<p>Several months ago (noting while an earlier post stated a year, first confirmed mention is April) Binance notified us they had cases where transactions were stuck, meaning they were not being mined successfully. We suggested Binance use RBF (replace by fee) on these transactions, which would replace the original transactions with a new transaction with a higher fee paid. Notably this was suggested because replace by fee invalidates the previous transaction (hence &ldquo;replace&rdquo;). As the transaction had RBF disabled, we recommended creating a new transaction manually, which would consume the same inputs to forcibly invalidate the previous transaction.</p>
<p>Some time later Binance notified us that they had account reconciliation issues. We were unable to reproduce those issues with the data we were given by Binance, but we suggested (months ago, now) using the <code>-zapwallettxes</code> command line option to mitigate the issue. This is notable as we believe this would have also prevented the issue seen.</p>
<p>Yesterday November 10th we were notified that previously stuck transactions had suddenly relayed successfully, post 1.14.5 update; likely because minfees have been lowered in 1.14.5, making the previously valid but unrelayable transactions relayable. The sole example we have, from Binance, is a transaction with fees which are valid as of v1.14.5, but were invalid (too low) in 1.14.3 and before. Note, Binance updated directly from v1.14.3 to 1.14.5, in the past few days.</p>
<p>Currently what we believe has happened is that the previously stuck transactions have been retried automatically, as would happen on each node restart after upgrade - and went through, since now the minimum required relay fee is lower. This is correct behaviour as a result of reducing fees.</p>
<h2 id="lessons">Lessons</h2>
<ul>
<li>Correct handling to cancel a transaction is to spend the to-be-cancelled transaction&rsquo;s inputs to a different transaction, which invalidates the first.
<ul>
<li>Ideally use replace-by-fee if available, but otherwise crafting and sending a transaction spending the previously chosen inputs, will invalidate the previous transaction.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Please note that transactions don&rsquo;t have a defined timeout period, but are typically disposed of due to memory limits.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="guidance">Guidance</h2>
<p>We have received no further reports of this happening. For any providers with concerns about stagnant invalid transactions, we recommend stopping the nodes, removing the mempool.dat file just in case, and then starting the node with -zapwallettxes.</p>
<p>For individual users with concerns, note that sending all of your Dogecoins back to yourself (ideally a new address, but you can use an existing one for this) will also spend any previous transaction outputs, and invalidate any such &ldquo;stuck&rdquo; transactions.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>Re-establishing the Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/announcements/2020-08-15-foundation-announcement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/announcements/2020-08-15-foundation-announcement/</guid><description>It is with great excitement that today we announce the re-establishment of the Dogecoin Foundation (est 2014), with a renewed focus on supporting the Dogecoin Ecosystem, Community and promoting the future of the Dogecoin Blockchain.
Focus The Dogecoin Foundation is not here to ‘take control’ of the Dogecoin Core Wallet project, which remains the primary reference implementation of a compliant Dogecoin Wallet. We are here to accelerate the development effort by supporting current Dogecoin Core and future Dogecoin Developers to work on a full-time basis through sponsorship, as well as providing a welcome landing for new contributors hoping to help with the project.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It is with great excitement that today we announce the re-establishment of the <strong>Dogecoin Foundation</strong> <em>(est 2014),</em> with a renewed focus on supporting the Dogecoin Ecosystem, Community and promoting the future of the Dogecoin Blockchain.</p>
<h3 id="focus">Focus</h3>
<p>The Dogecoin Foundation is not here to ‘take control’ of the <em>Dogecoin Core Wallet</em> project, which remains the primary reference implementation of a compliant Dogecoin Wallet. We are here to accelerate the development effort by supporting current Dogecoin Core and future Dogecoin Developers to work on a full-time basis through sponsorship, as well as providing a welcome landing for new contributors hoping to help with the project.</p>
<p>The Dogecoin Foundation is also looking to the future of the broader Dogecoin ecosystem, and in coming weeks, will be announcing new projects that will compliment the current Core Wallet to enable faster integration and easier APIs for Financial, Social and Charitable projects wishing to use Dogecoin. We believe that the success of Dogecoin is through broad global adoption and utility, and intend to focus on projects that increase Dogecoin uptake at a grassroots level.</p>
<h3 id="protecting-the-dogecoin-brand">Protecting the Dogecoin Brand</h3>
<p>For many years, the Dogecoin community has continued to think the best of people and hoped that everyone could play nicely with the name and logos. Dogecoin belongs to the people after all.</p>
<p>However, in recent times, numerous attempts have been made to co-opt the &lsquo;Dogecoin&rsquo; brand in various jurisdictions, in ways that would prevent the community and the project itself using them.</p>
<p>Not many people know this, but we would like to commend one Very Good Shibe: Jens Wiechers, who since 2014 has single-handedly and at great personal expense fought these kinds of attacks through the trademark office under the banner of the Dogecoin Foundation to protect everyone’s right to use the Dogecoin brand.</p>
<p>The Foundation holds the Dogecoin mark and the Dogecoin Logo and will maintain them for the community. This will mean the Foundation can continue to protect the Dogecoin Brand and allow (under a very liberal license) the ability to use it for Dogecoin-related memes, projects and fun. — We’ve got your back on this one.</p>
<h3 id="the-dogecoin-manifesto">The Dogecoin Manifesto</h3>
<p>We have been thinking about what Dogecoin means: as a technical project and as a movement for good in the world. We’ve condensed it down to four statements that we are calling the Dogecoin Manifesto. Two are technically-focused and two are social.</p>
<p>We believe that together, these key pillars that embody ‘Do Only Good Everyday’ will guide us forward as we make decisions and advance the Dogecoin ecosystem.</p>
<p><a href="/manifesto">The Dogecoin Manifesto</a></p>
<p>If you can, please ‘sign’ the Manifesto by clicking the tweet link at the bottom of the Manifesto page. This will let the world know what the Doge Army stands for!</p>
<h3 id="stop-collaborate-and-listen">Stop, collaborate and listen!</h3>
<p>One of the key tenets of the Manifesto is that we value <em>collaboration and trust</em> over <em>competition and exclusivity</em>. With that in mind, we have established a small, but intensely smart and amazing group of Advisors with experience in a range of areas who will be allies and advocates for Dogecoin as we seek to grow and develop the ecosystem.</p>
<p><a href="/about">Head on over and check out our amaze Advisors list</a>, and be sure to give them some love for offering their valuable time.</p>
<h3 id="the-cost-of-success">The cost of success</h3>
<p>The Foundation re-launches with the help of many volunteers who have been working tirelessly over the past several months. We recognise, however, that Dogecoin (at time of writing a 44 billion dollar financial product) has grown in size beyond many organisations with thousands of employees.</p>
<p>It has come to the point that many of the people who have been working non-stop to make Dogecoin what it is today whilst holding down full-time day jobs have been burning out and struggling to deal with the flood of attention (good and bad) that Dogecoin has been receiving.</p>
<p>This comes at a cost. Talented new people come to the project hoping to help and there is no one to welcome them or help them find a way to contribute and so they leave frustrated. The documentation effort has stalled and potential patches sit un-reviewed while the limited time a small core of people have is focused on critical issues.</p>
<h3 id="sponsorship">Sponsorship</h3>
<p>We believe Dogecoin deserves the attention of a team of full-time contributors who can help carry the burden of these more mundane tasks that keep the Dogecoin project alive.</p>
<p>The Foundation has been preparing a budget and has received expressions of interest from a number of people who are able to contribute. We aim to build a group of annual sponsors who can cover Foundation activities and a modest development team.</p>
<p>Our Initial target is to secure a three-year budget so that we can on-board a minimum staff to improve Dogecoin full-time, without them having to worry about job security.</p>
<p>If you are in a position to support the Dogecoin Foundation through major sponsorship please reach out, we’d love to speak with you.</p>
<p></br></br>
Much love,  — The Dogecoin Foundation
</br></br></p>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>