<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/</link><description>Recent content on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Statement Concerning the 'Dogecoin 2.0' crypto project</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/advisories/2021-08-31-advisory-dogecoin2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/advisories/2021-08-31-advisory-dogecoin2/</guid><description>A number of concerned Shibes from the Dogecoin community have recently brought to our attention the &amp;lsquo;Dogecoin 2.0&amp;rsquo; crypto project, which began earlier this year and has just announced listings on prominent exchanges.
As always, the Dogecoin Foundation welcomes newcomers to the crypto space but this project has no connection to or relationship with Dogecoin. To protect the Dogecoin community from being misled and to protect the Dogecoin name from possible misuse we have asked our brand protection lawyers to contact the developers of the &amp;lsquo;Dogecoin 2.</description></item><item><title>Claims of Affiliation with Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/advisories/2020-08-18-not-affiliated-moonrabbit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/advisories/2020-08-18-not-affiliated-moonrabbit/</guid><description>Neither the Dogecoin project, the Dogecoin Foundation or any affiliated developers or entities have partnered with MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu or any affiliated entities, including the purported Dogecoin Foundation using the domain doge.org. This purported organisation and domain are, as far as we have been able to ascertain, run by the same people who run MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu.
As such, any claim of &amp;ldquo;partnering up&amp;rdquo; appears to be designed to create a false appearance of partnership and association with the long-established Dogecoin project and Dogecoin Foundation.</description></item><item><title>Re-establishing the Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/announcements/2020-08-15-foundation-announcement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/announcements/2020-08-15-foundation-announcement/</guid><description>It is with great excitement that today we announce the re-establishment of the Dogecoin Foundation (est 2014), with a renewed focus on supporting the Dogecoin Ecosystem, Community and promoting the future of the Dogecoin Blockchain.
Focus The Dogecoin Foundation is not here to ‘take control’ of the Dogecoin Core Wallet project, which remains the primary reference implementation of a compliant Dogecoin Wallet. We are here to accelerate the development effort by supporting current Dogecoin Core and future Dogecoin Developers to work on a full-time basis through sponsorship, as well as providing a welcome landing for new contributors hoping to help with the project.</description></item><item><title>Dogecoin Foundation Roadmap</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/roadmap/</guid><description>Watch this space, technical &amp;amp; project roadmap for the Foundation is being drafted and will be announced shortly.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/about/</guid><description>About the foundation The Dogecoin Foundation is a not-for-profit organisation established to provide: Support for the Dogecoin crypto-currency through development and advocacy. Dogecoin trademark defense to prevent abuse and fraud. A roadmap and governance for the future of Dogecoin. History The Foundation was established by members of the Dogecoin team in 2014 to provide governance and support for the Dogecoin project. In 2021 the Foundation has been re invigorated by members of the original core team along with fresh faces and new seasoned advisors ready to grow Dogecoin for the decade ahead.</description></item><item><title>The Dogecoin Manifesto</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/manifesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/manifesto/</guid><description>We are Dogecoin, the accidental crypto-movement that makes people smile.
We are developing a currency for the people, and we strive to do only good everyday. Through this work we have come to value:
Being useful, we value utility over technical brilliance. Being personable, we value individuals and interactions over profit-driven economics. Being welcoming, we value collaboration and trust over competition and exclusivity. Being reliable, we value working solutions over speed of delivery.</description></item></channel></rss>