<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/</link><description>Recent content on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advisory: Response to transactions being automatically retried</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/posts/2021/11/advisory-response-to-transactions-being-automatically-retried/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/posts/2021/11/advisory-response-to-transactions-being-automatically-retried/</guid><description>Binance has today paused Dogecoin withdrawals and stated they have found a &amp;ldquo;major issue&amp;rdquo; in Doecoin. We wanted to address this:
Several months ago (noting while an earlier post stated a year, first confirmed mention is April) Binance notified us they had cases where transactions were stuck, meaning they were not being mined successfully. We suggested Binance use RBF (replace by fee) on these transactions, which would replace the original transactions with a new transaction with a higher fee paid.</description></item><item><title>Statement Concerning the 'Dogecoin 2.0' crypto project</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/advisories/2021-08-31-advisory-dogecoin2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/advisories/2021-08-31-advisory-dogecoin2/</guid><description>A number of concerned Shibes from the Dogecoin community have recently brought to our attention the &amp;lsquo;Dogecoin 2.0&amp;rsquo; crypto project, which began earlier this year and has just announced listings on prominent exchanges.
As always, the Dogecoin Foundation welcomes newcomers to the crypto space but this project has no connection to or relationship with Dogecoin. To protect the Dogecoin community from being misled and to protect the Dogecoin name from possible misuse we have asked our brand protection lawyers to contact the developers of the &amp;lsquo;Dogecoin 2.</description></item><item><title>Antydninger om tilknytting og samarbeid med Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/advisories/2020-08-18-not-affiliated-moonrabbit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/advisories/2020-08-18-not-affiliated-moonrabbit/</guid><description>Verken Dogecoin-prosjektet, Dogecoin-stiftelsen eller tilknyttede utviklere eller enheter har inngått samarbeid med MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu eller noen tilknyttede enheter, inkludert den påståtte Dogecoin -stiftelsen som bruker domenet doge.org. Denne påståtte organisasjonen og domenet drives, så langt vi har klart å fastslå, av de samme menneskene som driver MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu.
Som sådan ser det ut til at ethvert krav om &amp;ldquo;samarbeid og tilknytting&amp;rdquo; er utformet for å skape et misvisende bilde av samarbeid og tilknytning til det etablerte Dogecoin-prosjektet og Dogecoin Foundation.</description></item><item><title>Re-establishing the Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/announcements/2020-08-15-foundation-announcement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/announcements/2020-08-15-foundation-announcement/</guid><description>It is with great excitement that today we announce the re-establishment of the Dogecoin Foundation (est 2014), with a renewed focus on supporting the Dogecoin Ecosystem, Community and promoting the future of the Dogecoin Blockchain.
Focus The Dogecoin Foundation is not here to ‘take control’ of the Dogecoin Core Wallet project, which remains the primary reference implementation of a compliant Dogecoin Wallet. We are here to accelerate the development effort by supporting current Dogecoin Core and future Dogecoin Developers to work on a full-time basis through sponsorship, as well as providing a welcome landing for new contributors hoping to help with the project.</description></item><item><title>Dogecoin Foundation Roadmap</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/roadmap/</guid><description>Følg med på denne siden, Handlingsplaner for teknisk og prosjekt er under utarbeidelse og vil bli kunngjort snarlig.</description></item><item><title>Om oss</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/about/</guid><description>Om oss Dogecoinstiftelsen er en ideell organisasjon som er stiftet for : å være en forkjemper for kryptovalutaen Dogecoin å bidra til videreutviklingen av Dogecoin å beskytte varemerket Dogecoin og jobbe aktivt for å forhindre misbruk og svindel å lage en plan for fremtidig styring og utvikling av Dogecoin Historien Stiftelsen ble etablert i 2014 av utviklerne i Dogecoin for å støtte og videreutvikle prosjektet.</description></item><item><title>The Dogecoin Manifesto</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/manifesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/no/manifesto/</guid><description>Vi er Dogecoin, krypto-bevegelsen som ble til ved en tilfeldighet og som får folk til å smile.
Vi utvikler en folkelig digital valuta og vi streber hver dag for kun å gjøre godt.
Gjennom dette arbeidet har vi lært å sette pris på:
Å være til nytte, vi verdsetter nytteverdi fremfor teknisk briljans. Å være vennlig, vi verdsetter individer og relasjoner fremfor profittjag. Å være imøtekommende, vi verdsetter samarbeid og tillit fremfor konkurranse og enerett.</description></item></channel></rss>