<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/</link><description>Recent content on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shanties, RadioDoge &amp; Financial Freedom</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/blog/2022-04-11-shanty/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/blog/2022-04-11-shanty/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard the rousing tale of the whalers from Otakou and the Weller Bros trading company that plied its wares amongst them during the 1800s.
What you may not know is that the workers in these stories were often enticed with promises of a good wage, only to find themselves intentionally indebted to trading cooperatives who controlled 100% of the housing, equipment, trade and basic necessities in these remote regions.</description></item><item><title>Ross Nicoll Stepping into an Advisor Role for the Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/announcements/2022-02-24-update-ross/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/announcements/2022-02-24-update-ross/</guid><description>Recently Ross made public his decision to step back from involvement in the Foundation as a Director and more generally from active development in the crypto space.
While this is news to many in the community, Ross had made his intentions clear to the Core developers almost a year ago and has been working quietly behind the scenes to create a sustainable transition for his role in the Dogecoin project.</description></item><item><title>Let's talk about Development</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/blog/2022-02-15-tjstebbing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/blog/2022-02-15-tjstebbing/</guid><description>I know that for non-devs (or ‘not-yet-devs&amp;rsquo; 😉), it can sometimes be difficult to make sense of technical talk. I think that a part of my job as an Engineer at the Dogecoin Foundation is to explain technical things in terms non-tech folk can understand. Because of this, I’d like to ramble a bit about the Trailmap, about the goals we have and the projects that we’re hoping will fulfil them.</description></item><item><title>Dogecoin Foundation Update &amp; AMA on January 23rd, 2022</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/announcements/2022-01-21-update-ama/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/announcements/2022-01-21-update-ama/</guid><description>The Dogecoin Foundation, established and led by members of the original core development team and long-time members of the Dogecoin community, has responsibility for providing governance and support for the Dogecoin cryptocurrency project.
Since 2014, the Foundation&amp;rsquo;s sole mission has been to protect and support the Dogecoin project, its reputation, and the global community of Shibes. The Foundation is committed to ensuring that Dogecoin continues to thrive, and can ultimately scale to being a widely used currency whilst simultaneously tackling changes at a pace that keeps-up with other cryptocurrencies.</description></item><item><title>Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/trailmap/prologue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/trailmap/prologue/</guid><description>Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue เส้นทางของ Dogecoin : บทนำ โครงการ: การแปลงโฉมเว็บไซต์ Dogecoin.com และ สารานุกรมน้องหมา Dogepedia โครงการ: Libdogecoin โครงการ: มาตรฐาน Dogecoin - Dogecoin Standard โครงการ: กระเป๋าเงินกิกะ GigaWallet โครงการ: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) โครงการ: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) การนำเสนอโครงการ: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) การร่วมมือ: Point of Sale (L2 app) เส้นทาง DOGECOIN TRAILMAP คืออะไร แม้ว่า “Roadmap” (แผนการดำเนินงาน) จะเป็นคำที่มักใช้กันทั่วไปเมื่อมีการเปิดตัวสกุลเงินดิจิทัลใหม่ แต่กลับเป็นสิ่งที่บ่งบอกถึงทิศทางล่วงหน้าโดยมีบริษัทหรือ “ผู้นำ” ที่เป็นผู้กำหนดเพียงหนึ่งเดียว</description></item><item><title>Project: Dogecoin Standard</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/trailmap/standard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/trailmap/standard/</guid><description>Project: Dogecoin Standard เส้นทางของ Dogecoin : บทนำ โครงการ: การแปลงโฉมเว็บไซต์ Dogecoin.com และ สารานุกรมน้องหมา Dogepedia โครงการ: Libdogecoin โครงการ: มาตรฐาน Dogecoin - Dogecoin Standard โครงการ: กระเป๋าเงินกิกะ GigaWallet โครงการ: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) โครงการ: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) การนำเสนอโครงการ: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) การร่วมมือ: Point of Sale (L2 app) &amp;ldquo;มาตรฐาน Dogecoin Standard&amp;rdquo; - ข้อมูลจำเพาะ &amp;ldquo;Dogecoin Standard&amp;rdquo; จะเป็นข้อมูลจำเพาะที่เป็นลายลักษณ์อักษรและชุดทดสอบความถูกต้อง (Written Specification and validating test suite) ที่ได้มาจาก Dogecoin Core Wallet ระหว่างกระบวนการสร้าง Libdogecoin &amp;ldquo;Dogecoin Standard&amp;rdquo; มีจุดมุ่งหมายเพื่อจัดทำเอกสารเกี่ยวกับ Reference Implementation (Core Wallet) อย่างเต็มรูปแบบ เพื่อเติมเต็ม “Whitepaper” ที่มีการร้องขอบ่อย ๆ และเพื่อจัดเตรียมเอกสารให้แก่ทุกคนที่พยายามทำความเข้าใจการทำงานของ Dogecoin</description></item><item><title>Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp; Dogepedia</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/trailmap/website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/trailmap/website/</guid><description>Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp;amp; Dogepedia เส้นทางของ Dogecoin : บทนำ โครงการ: การแปลงโฉมเว็บไซต์ Dogecoin.com และ สารานุกรมน้องหมา Dogepedia โครงการ: Libdogecoin โครงการ: มาตรฐาน Dogecoin - Dogecoin Standard โครงการ: กระเป๋าเงินกิกะ GigaWallet โครงการ: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) โครงการ: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) การนำเสนอโครงการ: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) การร่วมมือ: Point of Sale (L2 app) การแปลงโฉมเว็บไซต์ Dogecoin.com อาสาสมัครจาก Doge Army ได้มารวมตัวกันจากทั่วทุกมุมโลกเพื่อออกแบบเว็บไซต์ Dogecoin.com Bluezr, CB, Florian และ Hack Club ที่วัยรุ่นอย่างเบล เอลล่า และแซมได้พัฒนาทั้งเว็บไซต์ ขึ้นมาใหม่ซึ่งมีข้อมูลใหม่ๆ เป็นกองพะเนินนั้น มีตั้งแต่ลิงก์ไปยังโครงการและทีมที่มีอยู่ต่างๆ ไปจนถึง ข้อมูลเกี่ยวกับเครือข่ายและวิธีที่คุณจะได้เข้าร่วมเป็นนักเข้ารหัส นักขุด นักสะสม หรือกระทั้งแฟนคลับ!</description></item><item><title>Project: GigaWallet</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/trailmap/gigawallet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/trailmap/gigawallet/</guid><description>Project: GigaWallet เส้นทางของ Dogecoin : บทนำ โครงการ: การแปลงโฉมเว็บไซต์ Dogecoin.com และ สารานุกรมน้องหมา Dogepedia โครงการ: Libdogecoin โครงการ: มาตรฐาน Dogecoin - Dogecoin Standard โครงการ: กระเป๋าเงินกิกะ GigaWallet โครงการ: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) โครงการ: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) การนำเสนอโครงการ: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) การร่วมมือ: Point of Sale (L2 app) &amp;ldquo;GIGAWALLET&amp;rdquo; เป็นการบริการที่จะช่วยบูรณาการการชำระเงินด้วย Dogecoin บนแพลตฟอร์มธุรกิจของคุณ Aเหมือนกับที่เราได้พูดไว้ในบทนำข้างต้น เราเชื่อว่าการที่สิ่งใดจะมีประโยชน์ได้นั้นต้องเกิดขึ้นหลังจากที่มีคนนำไปใช้ได้ และในทางกลับกันถ้าเราอยากให้มีการนำไปใช้กันอย่างแพร่หลายเราย่อมต้องสร้างสิ่งนั้นให้มีประโยชน์ ซึ่งในตอนนี้การนำไปใช้นั้นค่อนข้างยากและช้า หลายๆ แพล็ตฟอร์มจึงยังไม่สามารถนำ Dogecoin ไปใช้ได้</description></item><item><title>Project: Libdogecoin</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/trailmap/libdogecoin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/trailmap/libdogecoin/</guid><description>Project: Libdogecoin เส้นทางของ Dogecoin : บทนำ โครงการ: การแปลงโฉมเว็บไซต์ Dogecoin.com และ สารานุกรมน้องหมา Dogepedia โครงการ: Libdogecoin โครงการ: มาตรฐาน Dogecoin - Dogecoin Standard โครงการ: กระเป๋าเงินกิกะ GigaWallet โครงการ: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) โครงการ: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) การนำเสนอโครงการ: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) การร่วมมือ: Point of Sale (L2 app) &amp;ldquo;Libdogecoin&amp;rdquo; คือ clean C ไลบรารี่ของ Dogecoin บล็อคเชน &amp;ldquo;Libdogecoin&amp;rdquo; จะเป็นข้อกำหนดมาตรฐานของการนำไปใช้งานที่สมบูรณ์ ในรูปแบบของ C ไลบรารี่ ที่จะช่วยให้ใครก็ตามสามารถสร้างผลิตภัณฑ์ Dogecoin ได้โดยไม่ต้องกังวลกับข้อกำหนดที่ลึกลงไปใน การทำงานของบล็อคเชน</description></item><item><title>Advisory: Response to transactions being automatically retried</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/advisories/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/advisories/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</guid><description>Note: A previous version of this advisory used &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; to refer to a group separate to the Foundation. It has been edited to clarify.
Binance has today paused Dogecoin withdrawals and stated they have found a &amp;ldquo;minor issue&amp;rdquo; in Dogecoin. The Foundation wishes to address this:
Several months ago (noting while an earlier post stated a year, first confirmed mention is April) Binance notified a group of Dogecoin Core maintainers that Binance had cases where transactions were stuck, meaning the transactions were not being mined successfully.</description></item></channel></rss>