<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advisories on Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/advisories/</link><description>Recent content in Advisories on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/advisories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advisory: Response to transactions being automatically retried</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/advisories/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/advisories/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</guid><description>Note: A previous version of this advisory used &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; to refer to a group separate to the Foundation. It has been edited to clarify.
Binance has today paused Dogecoin withdrawals and stated they have found a &amp;ldquo;minor issue&amp;rdquo; in Dogecoin. The Foundation wishes to address this:
Several months ago (noting while an earlier post stated a year, first confirmed mention is April) Binance notified a group of Dogecoin Core maintainers that Binance had cases where transactions were stuck, meaning the transactions were not being mined successfully.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Note: A previous version of this advisory used &ldquo;we&rdquo; to refer to a group separate to the Foundation. It has been edited to
clarify.</p>
<p>Binance has today paused Dogecoin withdrawals and stated they have found a &ldquo;minor issue&rdquo; in Dogecoin. The Foundation wishes to address this:</p>
<p>Several months ago (noting while an earlier post stated a year, first confirmed mention is April) Binance notified a group of Dogecoin Core maintainers that Binance had cases where transactions were stuck, meaning the transactions were not being mined successfully. The maintainers suggested Binance use RBF (replace by fee) on these transactions, which would replace the original transactions with a new transaction with a higher fee paid. Notably this was suggested because replace by fee invalidates the previous transaction (hence &ldquo;replace&rdquo;). As the transaction had RBF disabled, it was recommended that Binance create a new transaction manually, which would consume the same inputs to forcibly invalidate the previous transaction.</p>
<p>Some time later Binance notified the maintainers that they had account reconciliation issues. The maintainers were unable to reproduce those issues with the data we were given by Binance, but at the time suggested using the <code>-zapwallettxes</code> command line option to mitigate the issue. This is notable as it is anticipated this would have also prevented the issue seen.</p>
<p>Yesterday November 10th Binance notified the maintainers that previously stuck transactions had suddenly relayed successfully, post 1.14.5 update; likely because minfees have been lowered in 1.14.5, making the previously valid but unrelayable transactions relayable. The sole example provided is a transaction with fees which are valid as of v1.14.5, but were invalid (too low) in 1.14.3 and before. Note, Binance updated directly from v1.14.3 to 1.14.5, in the past few days.</p>
<p>Based on the information available it appears that the previously stuck transactions have been retried automatically, as would happen on each node restart after upgrade - and went through, since now the minimum required relay fee is lower. This is correct behaviour as a result of reducing fees.</p>
<h2 id="lessons">Lessons</h2>
<ul>
<li>Correct handling to cancel a transaction is to spend the to-be-cancelled transaction&rsquo;s inputs to a different transaction, which invalidates the first.
<ul>
<li>Ideally use replace-by-fee if available, but otherwise crafting and sending a transaction spending the previously chosen inputs, will invalidate the previous transaction.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Please note that transactions don&rsquo;t have a defined timeout period, but are typically discarded due to memory limits.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="guidance">Guidance</h2>
<p>The Foundation has received no further reports of this happening. For any providers with concerns about stagnant invalid transactions, we recommend stopping the nodes, removing the mempool.dat file just in case, and then starting the node with <code>-zapwallettxes</code>.</p>
<p>For individual users with concerns, note that sending all of your Dogecoins back to yourself (ideally a new address, but you can use an existing one for this) will also spend any previous transaction outputs, and invalidate any such &ldquo;stuck&rdquo; transactions.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>Statement Concerning the 'Dogecoin 2.0' crypto project</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/advisories/2021-08-31-advisory-dogecoin2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/advisories/2021-08-31-advisory-dogecoin2/</guid><description>A number of concerned Shibes from the Dogecoin community have recently brought to our attention the &amp;lsquo;Dogecoin 2.0&amp;rsquo; crypto project, which began earlier this year and has just announced listings on prominent exchanges.
As always, the Dogecoin Foundation welcomes newcomers to the crypto space but this project has no connection to or relationship with Dogecoin. To protect the Dogecoin community from being misled and to protect the Dogecoin name from possible misuse we have asked our brand protection lawyers to contact the developers of the &amp;lsquo;Dogecoin 2.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A number of concerned Shibes from the Dogecoin community have recently brought to our attention the &lsquo;Dogecoin 2.0&rsquo;
crypto project, which began earlier this year and has just announced listings on prominent exchanges.</p>
<p>As always, the Dogecoin Foundation welcomes newcomers to the crypto space but this project has no connection to or
relationship with Dogecoin.  To protect the Dogecoin community from being misled and to protect the Dogecoin name
from possible misuse we have asked our brand protection lawyers to contact the developers of the &lsquo;Dogecoin 2.0&rsquo;
product.</p>
<p>We hope our reasonable request will see their development team select a new name for their project which does not
infringe on the rights and reputation of the Dogecoin project, and we look forward to any innovations they may make
in their future endeavours.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>คำแนะนำ: การพยายามของกลุ่มบุคคลที่อ้างว่ามีความร่วมมือกับทางมูลนิธิ</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/advisories/2020-08-18-not-affiliated-moonrabbit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/th/advisories/2020-08-18-not-affiliated-moonrabbit/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Dogecoin&amp;rdquo; และ &amp;ldquo;มูลนิธิ Dogecoin&amp;rdquo; รวมถึงนักพัฒนาของ &amp;ldquo;Dogecoin&amp;rdquo; ทุกคนไม่ได้เกี่ยวข้องหรือมีความร่วมมือใดๆกับ &amp;ldquo;MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu&amp;rdquo; และพวกเราไม่ได้เกี่ยวข้องกับ &amp;ldquo;Doge.org&amp;rdquo; ทั้งสิ้น (เราทราบมาว่าเว็บไซต์นี้บริหารโดย &amp;ldquo;MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu&amp;rdquo;)
การกล่าวอ้างว่ามีการร่วมมือกันนั้นระหว่างทั้งสององค์กรนั้นอาจทำให้เกิดความเข้าใจผิดต่อภาพลักษณ์ซึ่งอาจส่งผลร้ายต่อโครงการของมูลนิธิ และในระยะเวลาที่ผ่านมานั้นทาง &amp;ldquo;MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu&amp;rdquo; ได้มีความพยายามที่จะจดทะเบียนเครื่องหมายการค้า &amp;ldquo;Dogecoin&amp;rdquo; ทั้งในกลุ่มประเทศภาคพื้นยุโรปและสหรัฐอเมริกา ทำให้ทางมูลนิธิมีความจำเป็นต้องป้องกันต่อต้านการกระทำดังกล่าวที่อาจมีจุดประสงค์ที่ต้องการแสวงหาผลกำไรจากชื่อเสียงของ &amp;ldquo;Dogecoin&amp;rdquo; และอาจทำให้เจตนาที่ดีในการสร้าง &amp;ldquo;Dogecoin&amp;rdquo; ขึ้นมาตลอด 8 ปีนั้นต้องเสียหายและถูกเข้าใจผิดไปในทางที่ไม่ดีได้
สุดท้ายนี้พวกเราชาว &amp;ldquo;มูลนิธิ Dogecoin&amp;rdquo; จะขอยืนหยัดการต่อต้านการกระทำผิดและจะสืบหาข้อเท็จจริงต่างๆ ที่เกี่ยวข้องกับการกระทำดังกล่าวต่อไป และเพื่อป้องกันปัญหาที่อาจจะเกิดขึ้นในอนาคต พวกเราขอให้ทุกท่านที่ต้องการติดต่อกับทีมของ &amp;ldquo;Dogecoin&amp;rdquo; สามารถติดต่อโดยตรงที่เว็บไซต์ dogecoin.com และ foundation.dogecoin.com เพียงสองช่องทางเท่านั้น และกรุณาไม่ติดต่อกับผู้ที่อาจจะแอบอ้างเป็นตัวแทนของเราผ่านทางโซเชียลมีเดียหรือเว็บไซต์อื่นๆ</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>&ldquo;Dogecoin&rdquo; และ &ldquo;มูลนิธิ Dogecoin&rdquo; รวมถึงนักพัฒนาของ &ldquo;Dogecoin&rdquo; ทุกคนไม่ได้เกี่ยวข้องหรือมีความร่วมมือใดๆกับ &ldquo;MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu&rdquo; และพวกเราไม่ได้เกี่ยวข้องกับ &ldquo;Doge.org&rdquo; ทั้งสิ้น (เราทราบมาว่าเว็บไซต์นี้บริหารโดย &ldquo;MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu&rdquo;)</p>
<p>การกล่าวอ้างว่ามีการร่วมมือกันนั้นระหว่างทั้งสององค์กรนั้นอาจทำให้เกิดความเข้าใจผิดต่อภาพลักษณ์ซึ่งอาจส่งผลร้ายต่อโครงการของมูลนิธิ และในระยะเวลาที่ผ่านมานั้นทาง &ldquo;MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu&rdquo; ได้มีความพยายามที่จะจดทะเบียนเครื่องหมายการค้า &ldquo;Dogecoin&rdquo; ทั้งในกลุ่มประเทศภาคพื้นยุโรปและสหรัฐอเมริกา ทำให้ทางมูลนิธิมีความจำเป็นต้องป้องกันต่อต้านการกระทำดังกล่าวที่อาจมีจุดประสงค์ที่ต้องการแสวงหาผลกำไรจากชื่อเสียงของ &ldquo;Dogecoin&rdquo; และอาจทำให้เจตนาที่ดีในการสร้าง &ldquo;Dogecoin&rdquo; ขึ้นมาตลอด 8 ปีนั้นต้องเสียหายและถูกเข้าใจผิดไปในทางที่ไม่ดีได้</p>
<p>สุดท้ายนี้พวกเราชาว &ldquo;มูลนิธิ Dogecoin&rdquo; จะขอยืนหยัดการต่อต้านการกระทำผิดและจะสืบหาข้อเท็จจริงต่างๆ ที่เกี่ยวข้องกับการกระทำดังกล่าวต่อไป และเพื่อป้องกันปัญหาที่อาจจะเกิดขึ้นในอนาคต พวกเราขอให้ทุกท่านที่ต้องการติดต่อกับทีมของ &ldquo;Dogecoin&rdquo; สามารถติดต่อโดยตรงที่เว็บไซต์ <a href="https://dogecoin.com/">dogecoin.com</a> และ <a href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/">foundation.dogecoin.com</a> เพียงสองช่องทางเท่านั้น และกรุณาไม่ติดต่อกับผู้ที่อาจจะแอบอ้างเป็นตัวแทนของเราผ่านทางโซเชียลมีเดียหรือเว็บไซต์อื่นๆ</p>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>