<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/</link><description>Recent content on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shanties, RadioDoge &amp; Financial Freedom</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/blog/2022-04-11-shanty/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/blog/2022-04-11-shanty/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard the rousing tale of the whalers from Otakou and the Weller Bros trading company that plied it&amp;rsquo;s wares amongst them during the 1800s.
What you may not know is that the workers in these stories were often enticed with promises of a good wage, only to find themselves intentionally indebted to trading cooperatives who controlled 100% of the housing, equipment, trade and basic necessities in these remote regions.</description></item><item><title>Ross Nicoll Stepping into an Advisor Role for the Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/announcements/2022-02-24-update-ross/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/announcements/2022-02-24-update-ross/</guid><description>Recently Ross made public his decision to step back from involvement in the Foundation as a Director and more generally from active development in the crypto space.
While this is news to many in the community, Ross had made his intentions clear to the Core developers almost a year ago and has been working quietly behind the scenes to create a sustainable transition for his role in the Dogecoin project.</description></item><item><title>Let's talk about Development</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/blog/2022-02-15-tjstebbing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/blog/2022-02-15-tjstebbing/</guid><description>I know that for non-devs (or ‘not-yet-devs&amp;rsquo; 😉), it can sometimes be difficult to make sense of technical talk. I think that a part of my job as an Engineer at the Dogecoin Foundation is to explain technical things in terms non-tech folk can understand. Because of this, I’d like to ramble a bit about the Trailmap, about the goals we have and the projects that we’re hoping will fulfil them.</description></item><item><title>Dogecoin Foundation Update &amp; AMA on January 23rd, 2022</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/announcements/2022-01-21-update-ama/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/announcements/2022-01-21-update-ama/</guid><description>The Dogecoin Foundation, established and led by members of the original core development team and long-time members of the Dogecoin community, has responsibility for providing governance and support for the Dogecoin cryptocurrency project.
Since 2014, the Foundation&amp;rsquo;s sole mission has been to protect and support the Dogecoin project, its reputation, and the global community of Shibes. The Foundation is committed to ensuring that Dogecoin continues to thrive, and can ultimately scale to being a widely used currency whilst simultaneously tackling changes at a pace that keeps-up with other cryptocurrencies.</description></item><item><title>Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/trailmap/prologue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/trailmap/prologue/</guid><description>Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp;amp; Dogepedia Project: Libdogecoin Project: Dogecoin Standard Project: GigaWallet Project: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) Project: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) Proposal: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) Partnership: Point of Sale (L2 app) What is the Dogecoin Trailmap? While roadmap is a term that&amp;rsquo;s commonly used when new cryptocurrencies are released, it conveys a rigid way forward, led by a single company or &amp;rsquo;lead&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>Project: Dogecoin Standard</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/trailmap/standard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/trailmap/standard/</guid><description>Project: Dogecoin Standard Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp;amp; Dogepedia Project: Libdogecoin Project: Dogecoin Standard Project: GigaWallet Project: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) Project: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) Proposal: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) Partnership: Point of Sale (L2 app) Dogecoin Standard - A Specification. The Dogecoin Standard will be a Written Specification and validating test suite derived from the Dogecoin Core Wallet during the process of creating libdogecoin.</description></item><item><title>Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp; Dogepedia</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/trailmap/website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/trailmap/website/</guid><description>Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp;amp; Dogepedia Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp;amp; Dogepedia Project: Libdogecoin Project: Dogecoin Standard Project: GigaWallet Project: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) Project: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) Proposal: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) Partnership: Point of Sale (L2 app) Dogecoin.com makeover. Volunteers from the Doge Army have come together from all over the world to work on a re-design of the Dogecoin.</description></item><item><title>Project: GigaWallet</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/trailmap/gigawallet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/trailmap/gigawallet/</guid><description>Project: GigaWallet Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp;amp; Dogepedia Project: Libdogecoin Project: Dogecoin Standard Project: GigaWallet Project: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) Project: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) Proposal: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) Partnership: Point of Sale (L2 app) GigaWallet, an enterprise-ready dogecoin service for your platform. As we&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned in the Prologue, we believe that utility comes from adoption and adoption comes from utility, it&amp;rsquo;s a feedback loop that is on the slow path right now due to friction around platform adoption.</description></item><item><title>Project: Libdogecoin</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/trailmap/libdogecoin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/trailmap/libdogecoin/</guid><description>Project: Libdogecoin Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp;amp; Dogepedia Project: Libdogecoin Project: Dogecoin Standard Project: GigaWallet Project: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) Project: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) Proposal: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) Partnership: Point of Sale (L2 app) Libdogecoin, a clean C library of Dogecoin building blocks. Libdogecoin will be a complete implementation of the Dogecoin Protocols, as a C library (and series of bindings to popular languages) which will allow anyone to build a Dogecoin compliant product, without needing to worry about the deeper specifics of the crypto functions.</description></item><item><title>Pernyataan: Respons terhadap transaksi yang dicoba ulang secara otomatis</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/advisories/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/advisories/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</guid><description>Catatan: Versi sebelumnya dari nasihat ini menggunakan &amp;ldquo;kami&amp;rdquo; untuk merujuk ke grup yang terpisah dari Yayasan. Itu sudah diedit sebagai klarifikasi
Binance hari ini telah menghentikan penarikan Dogecoin dan menyatakan bahwa mereka telah menemukan &amp;ldquo;masalah kecil&amp;rdquo; di Dogecoin. Yayasan mengharapkan klarifikasi hal ini:
Beberapa bulan yang lalu (mencatat sementara posting sebelumnya menyatakan satu tahun, penyebutan pertama yang dikonfirmasi adalah April) Binance memberi tahu sekelompok pengelola Dogecoin Core bahwa Binance memiliki kasus di mana transaksi macet, yang berarti transaksi tidak berhasil ditambang.</description></item></channel></rss>