<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Development Blog 27th September 2023</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2023-09-27-devblog/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2023-09-27-devblog/</guid><description>Happy September Shibes! We’ve been busy working on a number of things, and we wanted to share some of the progress we’ve made. The last blog contained bullet points of the things we were working on. In this post we’ll go into more detail on some of the items, and we’ll also share some new things that we’ve been working on.
libdogecoin 0.1.3 In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore some of the features introduced in libdogecoin 0.</description></item><item><title>Development Blog 12th August 2023</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2023-08-12-devblog/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2023-08-12-devblog/</guid><description>Ahoy Shibes, in recognition of the fact that devs are usually good at coding but frequently bad at talking, we’re going to have a shot at maintaining a fortnightly dev-blog for the Dogecoin work going on at the foundation. Not entirely sure if the format will remain the same as we go but it’s a start!
Here’s an overview of the last 2 weeks:
Libdogecoin - Low level C library for building Dogecoin systems</description></item><item><title>Fantoumi's questions</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2022-12-20-fantoumi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2022-12-20-fantoumi/</guid><description>2022 has been a busy time for the Dogecoin Foundation, there have been solid developments and improvements within the Dogecoin Ecosystem, we’ve had a hugely successful Hackathon that’s seen many new people introduced to Dogecoin development, and we’ve been able to grow our team through the kind generosity of some big Shibes who are aligned with our mission and want to see us succeed.
That said there’s been a growing anxiety in the community around a couple of topics which have been taken far out of proportion by a small number of people who seem intent on dividing the community rather than working toward consensus.</description></item><item><title>Oona wants to say a thing</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2022-12-14-oonabot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2022-12-14-oonabot/</guid><description>In the spirit of improving communications and transparency I’d like to take the opportunity to rip the Band-Aid off and let it be known that I have been a volunteer with the Dogecoin Foundation for the past six months. Some of you may remember that in June around my birthday I was invited by members of the Foundation for dinner in Austin. It was an absolutely amazing evening getting to know these people in person.</description></item><item><title>Shibes raise more than 1,000,000 Dogecoin ($100,000) to build a statue of the Doge!</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2022-12-06-bronzethedoge-success/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2022-12-06-bronzethedoge-success/</guid><description>In celebration of Kabosu the Doge&amp;rsquo;s 17th birthday, shibes around the world have raised more than 1,000,000 Dogecoin ($100,000) in donations which will be used to create a bronze statue of Kabosu in her home city of Sakura, Japan. Kabosu&amp;rsquo;s owner, Atsuko Sato was kind enough to reach out to Sakura city council, who support the idea of including the statue in their 2024 project to revitalise Furusato Square.
The funds which were raised have been moved into a multisignature wallet and now the work to make the statue of our beloved Doge a reality begins.</description></item><item><title>Shanties, RadioDoge &amp; Financial Freedom</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2022-04-11-shanty/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2022-04-11-shanty/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard the rousing tale of the whalers from Otakou and the Weller Bros trading company that plied its wares amongst them during the 1800s.
What you may not know is that the workers in these stories were often enticed with promises of a good wage, only to find themselves intentionally indebted to trading cooperatives who controlled 100% of the housing, equipment, trade and basic necessities in these remote regions.</description></item><item><title>Let's talk about Development</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2022-02-15-tjstebbing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/blog/2022-02-15-tjstebbing/</guid><description>I know that for non-devs (or ‘not-yet-devs&amp;rsquo; 😉), it can sometimes be difficult to make sense of technical talk. I think that a part of my job as an Engineer at the Dogecoin Foundation is to explain technical things in terms non-tech folk can understand. Because of this, I’d like to ramble a bit about the Trailmap, about the goals we have and the projects that we’re hoping will fulfil them.</description></item></channel></rss>