<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/</link><description>Recent content on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advisory: Response to transactions being automatically retried</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</guid><description>Binance has today paused Dogecoin withdrawals and stated they have found a &amp;ldquo;minor issue&amp;rdquo; in Dogecoin. We wanted to address this:
Several months ago (noting while an earlier post stated a year, first confirmed mention is April) Binance notified us they had cases where transactions were stuck, meaning they were not being mined successfully. We suggested Binance use RBF (replace by fee) on these transactions, which would replace the original transactions with a new transaction with a higher fee paid.</description></item><item><title>Conselho: Comunicado em relação ao projeto cripto 'Dogecoin 2.0'</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/2021-08-31-advisory-dogecoin2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/2021-08-31-advisory-dogecoin2/</guid><description>Alguns Shibes preocupados da comunidade Dogecoin recentemente trouxeram à nossa atenção o projeto cripto &amp;lsquo;Dogecoin 2.0&amp;rsquo;, que começou no início deste ano e acabou de anunciar que vai ser listado em exchanges de renome.
Como de costume, a Fundação Dogecoin dá as boas vindas aos recém-chegados ao espaço cripto, mas este projeto não tem nenhuma ligação ou conexão com Dogecoin. Para proteger a comunidade Dogecoin de ser induzida em erro e para proteger o nome da Dogecoin de ser usado indevidamente, nós pedimos aos nossos advogados de proteção de marca para contatar os criadores do produto &amp;lsquo;Dogecoin 2.</description></item><item><title>Claims of Affiliation with Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/2020-08-18-not-affiliated-moonrabbit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/2020-08-18-not-affiliated-moonrabbit/</guid><description>Neither the Dogecoin project, the Dogecoin Foundation or any affiliated developers or entities have partnered with MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu or any affiliated entities, including the purported Dogecoin Foundation using the domain doge.org. This purported organisation and domain are, as far as we have been able to ascertain, run by the same people who run MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu.
As such, any claim of &amp;ldquo;partnering up&amp;rdquo; appears to be designed to create a false appearance of partnership and association with the long-established Dogecoin project and Dogecoin Foundation.</description></item><item><title>Re-establishing the Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/announcements/2020-08-15-foundation-announcement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/announcements/2020-08-15-foundation-announcement/</guid><description>It is with great excitement that today we announce the re-establishment of the Dogecoin Foundation (est 2014), with a renewed focus on supporting the Dogecoin Ecosystem, Community and promoting the future of the Dogecoin Blockchain.
Focus The Dogecoin Foundation is not here to ‘take control’ of the Dogecoin Core Wallet project, which remains the primary reference implementation of a compliant Dogecoin Wallet. We are here to accelerate the development effort by supporting current Dogecoin Core and future Dogecoin Developers to work on a full-time basis through sponsorship, as well as providing a welcome landing for new contributors hoping to help with the project.</description></item><item><title>Roteiro da Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/roadmap/</guid><description>Fique atento a este espaço, o plano de trabalho e plano técnico para a Fundação estão a ser criados e serão anunciados brevemente.</description></item><item><title>Sobre Nós</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/about/</guid><description>Sobre Nós A Dogecoin Foundation é uma organização sem fins lucrativos criada para fornecer: Apoiar a criptomoeda Dogecoin via desenvolvimento e apoio público. Defesa da marca Dogecoin para prevenir abuso e fraude. Um roteiro e administração para um futuro da Dogecoin. Histórico A fundação foi estabelecida por membros da equipa da Dogecoin em 2014 para fornecer administração e apoio para o projeto dogecoin.</description></item><item><title>O Manifesto Dogecoin</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/manifesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/manifesto/</guid><description>Nós somos Dogecoin, o movimento crypto - acidental que faz as pessoas sorrir.
Nós estamos a desenvolver uma moeda para o povo, e esforçamo-nos para praticar o bem todos os dias. Através deste trabalho nós aprendemos a valorizar:
Ser útil, nós valorizamos mais utilidade do que boas técnicas. Ser amigável, nós valorizamos mais indivíduos e as suas interações do que economias com fins lucrativos. Ser hospitaleiro, nós valorizamos mais a colaboração e confiança do que competição e exclusividade.</description></item></channel></rss>