<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/</link><description>Recent content on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advisory: Claims of Affiliation with Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/posts/2021/08/advisory-claims-of-affiliation-with-dogecoin-foundation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/posts/2021/08/advisory-claims-of-affiliation-with-dogecoin-foundation/</guid><description>Neither the Dogecoin project, the Dogecoin Foundation or any affiliated developers or entities have partnered with MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu or any affiliated entities, including the purported Dogecoin Foundation using the domain doge.org. This purported organisation and domain are, as far as we have been able to ascertain, run by the same people who run MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu.
As such, any claim of &amp;ldquo;partnering up&amp;rdquo; appears to be designed to create a false appearance of partnership and association with the long-established Dogecoin project and Dogecoin Foundation.</description></item><item><title>Announcement: Re-establishing the Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/posts/2021/08/announcement-re-establishing-the-dogecoin-foundation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/posts/2021/08/announcement-re-establishing-the-dogecoin-foundation/</guid><description>It is with great excitement that today we announce the re-establishment of the Dogecoin Foundation (est 2014), with a renewed focus on supporting the Dogecoin Ecosystem, Community and promoting the future of the Dogecoin Blockchain.
Focus The Dogecoin Foundation is not here to ‘take control’ of the Dogecoin Core Wallet project, which remains the primary reference implementation of a compliant Dogecoin Wallet. We are here to accelerate the development effort by supporting current Dogecoin Core and future Dogecoin Developers to work on a full-time basis through sponsorship, as well as providing a welcome landing for new contributors hoping to help with the project.</description></item><item><title>Dogecoin Foundation Roadmap</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/roadmap/</guid><description>Watch this space, technical &amp;amp; project roadmap for the Foundation is being drafted and will be announced shortly.</description></item><item><title>Sobre Nós</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/about/</guid><description>A Dogecoin Foundation é uma organização sem fins lucrativos criada para fornecer:
Apoiar a criptomoeda Dogecoin via desenvolvimento e apoio público. Defesa da marca Dogecoin para prevenir abuso e fraude. Um roteiro e administração para um futuro da Dogecoin. Histórico A fundação foi estabelecida por membros da equipa da Dogecoin em 2014 para fornecer administração e apoio para o projeto dogecoin. Em 2021 a fundação foi revigorada por membros da equipa original juntamente com novas caras e novos conselheiros veteranos prontos para crescer Dogecoin para a década seguinte.</description></item><item><title>The Dogecoin Manifesto</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/manifesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/manifesto/</guid><description>We are Dogecoin, the accidental crypto- movement that makes people smile.
We are developing a currency for the people, and we strive to do only good everyday. Through this work we have come to value:
Being useful, we value utility over technical brilliance. Being personable, we value individuals and interactions over profit-driven economics. Being welcoming, we value collaboration and trust over competition and exclusivity. Being reliable, we value working solutions over speed of delivery.</description></item></channel></rss>