<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advisory: Claims of Affiliation with Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/posts/2021/08/advisory-claims-of-affiliation-with-dogecoin-foundation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/posts/2021/08/advisory-claims-of-affiliation-with-dogecoin-foundation/</guid><description>Neither the Dogecoin project, the Dogecoin Foundation or any affiliated developers or entities have partnered with MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu or any affiliated entities, including the purported Dogecoin Foundation using the domain doge.org. This purported organisation and domain are, as far as we have been able to ascertain, run by the same people who run MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu.
As such, any claim of &amp;ldquo;partnering up&amp;rdquo; appears to be designed to create a false appearance of partnership and association with the long-established Dogecoin project and Dogecoin Foundation.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Neither the Dogecoin project, the Dogecoin Foundation or any affiliated developers or entities have partnered with MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu or any affiliated entities, including the purported Dogecoin Foundation using the domain doge.org. This purported organisation and domain are, as far as we have been able to ascertain, run by the same people who run MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu.</p>
<p>As such, any claim of &ldquo;partnering up&rdquo; appears to be designed to create a false appearance of partnership and association with the long-established Dogecoin project and Dogecoin Foundation.</p>
<p>We should also note that the MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu corporation is actively attempting to register a trademark for the &ldquo;Dogecoin&rdquo; name in both Europe as well as the United States. The Dogecoin Project and the Dogecoin Foundation are actively in the process of opposing these and other bad faith attempts to register such trademarks on the grounds that those entities have no connection to Dogecoin and are attempting to profit unfairly off of the goodwill Dogecoin has built over the last eight years since its inception.</p>
<p>Please be assured that we are making all necessary investigations to ascertain the facts in this rapidly evolving matter. For the avoidance of doubt, enquires should be directed to members of the Dogecoin Project, the Dogecoin Core developers, and the Dogecoin Foundation only through channels listed on either <a href="https://dogecoin.com/">dogecoin.com</a> or <a href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/">foundation.dogecoin.com</a> and not through any other email, social media acccount or website purported to be affiliated with Dogecoin.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>Announcement: Re-establishing the Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/posts/2021/08/announcement-re-establishing-the-dogecoin-foundation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/posts/2021/08/announcement-re-establishing-the-dogecoin-foundation/</guid><description>It is with great excitement that today we announce the re-establishment of the Dogecoin Foundation (est 2014), with a renewed focus on supporting the Dogecoin Ecosystem, Community and promoting the future of the Dogecoin Blockchain.
Focus The Dogecoin Foundation is not here to ‘take control’ of the Dogecoin Core Wallet project, which remains the primary reference implementation of a compliant Dogecoin Wallet. We are here to accelerate the development effort by supporting current Dogecoin Core and future Dogecoin Developers to work on a full-time basis through sponsorship, as well as providing a welcome landing for new contributors hoping to help with the project.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It is with great excitement that today we announce the re-establishment of the <strong>Dogecoin Foundation</strong> <em>(est 2014),</em> with a renewed focus on supporting the Dogecoin Ecosystem, Community and promoting the future of the Dogecoin Blockchain.</p>
<h3 id="focus">Focus</h3>
<p>The Dogecoin Foundation is not here to ‘take control’ of the <em>Dogecoin Core Wallet</em> project, which remains the primary reference implementation of a compliant Dogecoin Wallet. We are here to accelerate the development effort by supporting current Dogecoin Core and future Dogecoin Developers to work on a full-time basis through sponsorship, as well as providing a welcome landing for new contributors hoping to help with the project.</p>
<p>The Dogecoin Foundation is also looking to the future of the broader Dogecoin ecosystem, and in coming weeks, will be announcing new projects that will compliment the current Core Wallet to enable faster integration and easier APIs for Financial, Social and Charitable projects wishing to use Dogecoin. We believe that the success of Dogecoin is through broad global adoption and utility, and intend to focus on projects that increase Dogecoin uptake at a grassroots level.</p>
<h3 id="protecting-the-dogecoin-brand">Protecting the Dogecoin Brand</h3>
<p>For many years, the Dogecoin community has continued to think the best of people and hoped that everyone could play nicely with the name and logos. Dogecoin belongs to the people after all.</p>
<p>However, in recent times, numerous attempts have been made to co-opt the &lsquo;Dogecoin&rsquo; brand in various jurisdictions, in ways that would prevent the community and the project itself using them.</p>
<p>Not many people know this, but we would like to commend one Very Good Shibe: Jens Wiechers, who since 2014 has single-handedly and at great personal expense fought these kinds of attacks through the trademark office under the banner of the Dogecoin Foundation to protect everyone’s right to use the Dogecoin brand.</p>
<p>The Foundation holds the Dogecoin mark and the Dogecoin Logo and will maintain them for the community. This will mean the Foundation can continue to protect the Dogecoin Brand and allow (under a very liberal license) the ability to use it for Dogecoin-related memes, projects and fun. — We’ve got your back on this one.</p>
<h3 id="the-dogecoin-manifesto">The Dogecoin Manifesto</h3>
<p>We have been thinking about what Dogecoin means: as a technical project and as a movement for good in the world. We’ve condensed it down to four statements that we are calling the Dogecoin Manifesto. Two are technically-focused and two are social.</p>
<p>We believe that together, these key pillars that embody ‘Do Only Good Everyday’ will guide us forward as we make decisions and advance the Dogecoin ecosystem.</p>
<p><a href="/manifesto">The Dogecoin Manifesto</a></p>
<p>If you can, please ‘sign’ the Manifesto by clicking the tweet link at the bottom of the Manifesto page. This will let the world know what the Doge Army stands for!</p>
<h3 id="stop-collaborate-and-listen">Stop, collaborate and listen!</h3>
<p>One of the key tenets of the Manifesto is that we value <em>collaboration and trust</em> over <em>competition and exclusivity</em>. With that in mind, we have established a small, but intensely smart and amazing group of Advisors with experience in a range of areas who will be allies and advocates for Dogecoin as we seek to grow and develop the ecosystem.</p>
<p><a href="/about">Head on over and check out our amaze Advisors list</a>, and be sure to give them some love for offering their valuable time.</p>
<h3 id="the-cost-of-success">The cost of success</h3>
<p>The Foundation re-launches with the help of many volunteers who have been working tirelessly over the past several months. We recognise, however, that Dogecoin (at time of writing a 44 billion dollar financial product) has grown in size beyond many organisations with thousands of employees.</p>
<p>It has come to the point that many of the people who have been working non-stop to make Dogecoin what it is today whilst holding down full-time day jobs have been burning out and struggling to deal with the flood of attention (good and bad) that Dogecoin has been receiving.</p>
<p>This comes at a cost. Talented new people come to the project hoping to help and there is no one to welcome them or help them find a way to contribute and so they leave frustrated. The documentation effort has stalled and potential patches sit un-reviewed while the limited time a small core of people have is focused on critical issues.</p>
<h3 id="sponsorship">Sponsorship</h3>
<p>We believe Dogecoin deserves the attention of a team of full-time contributors who can help carry the burden of these more mundane tasks that keep the Dogecoin project alive.</p>
<p>The Foundation has been preparing a budget and has received expressions of interest from a number of people who are able to contribute. We aim to build a group of annual sponsors who can cover Foundation activities and a modest development team.</p>
<p>Our Initial target is to secure a three-year budget so that we can on-board a minimum staff to improve Dogecoin full-time, without them having to worry about job security.</p>
<p>If you are in a position to support the Dogecoin Foundation through major sponsorship please reach out, we’d love to speak with you.</p>
<p></br></br>
Much love,  — The Dogecoin Foundation
</br></br></p>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>