<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advisories on Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/advisories/</link><description>Recent content in Advisories on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/advisories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advisory: Response to transactions being automatically retried</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/advisories/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/advisories/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</guid><description>Binance has today paused Dogecoin withdrawals and stated they have found a &amp;ldquo;minor issue&amp;rdquo; in Dogecoin. We wanted to address this:
Several months ago (noting while an earlier post stated a year, first confirmed mention is April) Binance notified us they had cases where transactions were stuck, meaning they were not being mined successfully. We suggested Binance use RBF (replace by fee) on these transactions, which would replace the original transactions with a new transaction with a higher fee paid.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Binance has today paused Dogecoin withdrawals and stated they have found a &ldquo;minor issue&rdquo; in Dogecoin. We wanted to address this:</p>
<p>Several months ago (noting while an earlier post stated a year, first confirmed mention is April) Binance notified us they had cases where transactions were stuck, meaning they were not being mined successfully. We suggested Binance use RBF (replace by fee) on these transactions, which would replace the original transactions with a new transaction with a higher fee paid. Notably this was suggested because replace by fee invalidates the previous transaction (hence &ldquo;replace&rdquo;). As the transaction had RBF disabled, we recommended creating a new transaction manually, which would consume the same inputs to forcibly invalidate the previous transaction.</p>
<p>Some time later Binance notified us that they had account reconciliation issues. We were unable to reproduce those issues with the data we were given by Binance, but we suggested (months ago, now) using the <code>-zapwallettxes</code> command line option to mitigate the issue. This is notable as we believe this would have also prevented the issue seen.</p>
<p>Yesterday November 10th we were notified that previously stuck transactions had suddenly relayed successfully, post 1.14.5 update; likely because minfees have been lowered in 1.14.5, making the previously valid but unrelayable transactions relayable. The sole example we have, from Binance, is a transaction with fees which are valid as of v1.14.5, but were invalid (too low) in 1.14.3 and before. Note, Binance updated directly from v1.14.3 to 1.14.5, in the past few days.</p>
<p>Currently what we believe has happened is that the previously stuck transactions have been retried automatically, as would happen on each node restart after upgrade - and went through, since now the minimum required relay fee is lower. This is correct behaviour as a result of reducing fees.</p>
<h2 id="lessons">Lessons</h2>
<ul>
<li>Correct handling to cancel a transaction is to spend the to-be-cancelled transaction&rsquo;s inputs to a different transaction, which invalidates the first.
<ul>
<li>Ideally use replace-by-fee if available, but otherwise crafting and sending a transaction spending the previously chosen inputs, will invalidate the previous transaction.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Please note that transactions don&rsquo;t have a defined timeout period, but are typically disposed of due to memory limits.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="guidance">Guidance</h2>
<p>We have received no further reports of this happening. For any providers with concerns about stagnant invalid transactions, we recommend stopping the nodes, removing the mempool.dat file just in case, and then starting the node with -zapwallettxes.</p>
<p>For individual users with concerns, note that sending all of your Dogecoins back to yourself (ideally a new address, but you can use an existing one for this) will also spend any previous transaction outputs, and invalidate any such &ldquo;stuck&rdquo; transactions.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>Saran: Pernyataan Mengenai proyek kripto 'Dogecoin 2.0'</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/advisories/2021-08-31-advisory-dogecoin2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/advisories/2021-08-31-advisory-dogecoin2/</guid><description>Sejumlah Shibe yang peduli dari komunitas Dogecoin baru-baru ini menarik perhatian kami pada proyek kripto &amp;lsquo;Dogecoin 2.0&amp;rsquo; , yang dimulai awal tahun ini dan baru saja mengumumkan listing di bursa terkemuka.
Seperti biasa, Yayasan Dogecoin menyambut pendatang baru di ruang kripto tetapi proyek ini tidak memiliki hubungan dengan atau hubungan dengan Dogecoin. Untuk melindungi komunitas Dogecoin agar tidak disesatkan dan untuk melindungi nama Dogecoin dari kemungkinan penyalahgunaan, kami telah meminta pengacara perlindungan merek kami untuk menghubungi pengembang &amp;lsquo;Dogecoin 2.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Sejumlah Shibe yang peduli dari komunitas Dogecoin baru-baru ini menarik perhatian kami pada proyek kripto &lsquo;Dogecoin 2.0&rsquo;
, yang dimulai awal tahun ini dan baru saja mengumumkan listing di bursa terkemuka.</p>
<p>Seperti biasa, Yayasan Dogecoin menyambut pendatang baru di ruang kripto tetapi proyek ini tidak memiliki hubungan dengan atau
hubungan dengan Dogecoin. Untuk melindungi komunitas Dogecoin agar tidak disesatkan dan untuk melindungi nama Dogecoin
dari kemungkinan penyalahgunaan, kami telah meminta pengacara perlindungan merek kami untuk menghubungi pengembang &lsquo;Dogecoin 2.0&rsquo;
produk.</p>
<p>Kami berharap permintaan wajar kami akan melihat tim pengembangan mereka memilih nama baru untuk proyek mereka yang tidak
melanggar hak dan reputasi proyek Dogecoin, dan kami menantikan inovasi apa pun yang mungkin mereka buat
dalam usaha masa depan mereka.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>Saran: Klaim Afiliasi dengan Yayasan Dogecoin</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/advisories/2020-08-18-not-affiliated-moonrabbit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/id/advisories/2020-08-18-not-affiliated-moonrabbit/</guid><description>Baik proyek Dogecoin, Yayasan Dogecoin, atau pengembang atau entitas afiliasi mana pun tidak bermitra dengan MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu atau entitas afiliasi apa pun, termasuk Yayasan Dogecoin yang mengaku menggunakan domain doge.org. Organisasi dan domain yang diklaim ini, sejauh yang kami dapat pastikan, dijalankan oleh orang yang sama yang menjalankan MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu.
Dengan demikian, setiap klaim &amp;ldquo;bermitra&amp;rdquo; tampaknya dirancang untuk menciptakan tampilan kemitraan dan asosiasi yang salah dengan proyek Dogecoin dan Yayasan Dogecoin yang sudah lama berdiri.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Baik proyek Dogecoin, Yayasan Dogecoin, atau pengembang atau entitas afiliasi mana pun tidak bermitra dengan MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu atau entitas afiliasi apa pun, termasuk Yayasan Dogecoin yang mengaku menggunakan domain doge.org. Organisasi dan domain yang diklaim ini, sejauh yang kami dapat pastikan, dijalankan oleh orang yang sama yang menjalankan MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu.</p>
<p>Dengan demikian, setiap klaim &ldquo;bermitra&rdquo; tampaknya dirancang untuk menciptakan tampilan kemitraan dan asosiasi yang salah dengan proyek Dogecoin dan Yayasan Dogecoin yang sudah lama berdiri.</p>
<p>Kami juga harus mencatat bahwa perusahaan MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu secara aktif berusaha untuk mendaftarkan merek dagang untuk nama &ldquo;Dogecoin&rdquo; di Eropa maupun Amerika Serikat. Proyek Dogecoin dan Yayasan Dogecoin secara aktif dalam proses menentang ini dan upaya itikad buruk lainnya untuk mendaftarkan merek dagang tersebut dengan alasan bahwa entitas tersebut tidak memiliki hubungan dengan Dogecoin dan berusaha untuk mendapatkan keuntungan secara tidak adil dari niat baik yang telah dibangun Dogecoin atas delapan tahun terakhir sejak didirikan.</p>
<p>Yakinlah bahwa kami melakukan semua penyelidikan yang diperlukan untuk memastikan fakta dalam masalah yang berkembang pesat ini. Untuk menghindari keraguan, pertanyaan harus ditujukan kepada anggota Proyek Dogecoin, pengembang Inti Dogecoin, dan Yayasan Dogecoin hanya melalui saluran yang terdaftar di <a href="https://dogecoin.com/">dogecoin.com</a> atau <a href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/">foundation.dogecoin.com</a> dan tidak melalui email, akun media sosial, atau situs web lain yang mengaku berafiliasi dengan Dogecoin.</p>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>