<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Announcements on Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/announcements/</link><description>Recent content in Announcements on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/announcements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ross Nicoll Stepping into an Advisor Role for the Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/announcements/2022-02-24-update-ross/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/announcements/2022-02-24-update-ross/</guid><description>Recently Ross made public his decision to step back from involvement in the Foundation as a Director and more generally from active development in the crypto space.
While this is news to many in the community, Ross had made his intentions clear to the Core developers almost a year ago and has been working quietly behind the scenes to create a sustainable transition for his role in the Dogecoin project.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Recently Ross <a href="https://rnicoll.name/posts/2022-02-16-stepping-away/">made public his decision</a> to
step back from involvement in the Foundation as a Director and more generally from
active development in the crypto space.</p>
<p>While this is news to many in the community, Ross had made his intentions clear to
the Core developers almost a year ago and has been working quietly behind the scenes
to create a sustainable transition for his role in the Dogecoin project.</p>
<p>With this in mind, Ross has been instrumental in the re-establishment of the Dogecoin
Foundation in 2021. The Foundation has been set up to ensure that Dogecoin prospers
into the future through a diverse ecosystem of projects and teams, working in
collaboration toward making Dogecoin a long-term sustainable cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>While this may be seen as a loss for the Dogecoin Community, we believe that Ross'
ongoing involvement as an Advisor will free him up to play more of an advocacy role.
On behalf of the Dogecoin Foundation and the wider Dogecoin community, we salute Ross
for his tireless work on maintaining the Dogecoin dream for most of the last decade.</p>
<p>We will miss the top hat, the easy going British humour, and the boundless wisdom in
our day-to-day interactions, and we wish Ross a bright and happy future as he continues
to Do Only Good Everyday.</p>
<p>&ndash; The Dogecoin Foundation crew.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>Dogecoin Foundation Update &amp; AMA on January 23rd, 2022</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/announcements/2022-01-21-update-ama/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/announcements/2022-01-21-update-ama/</guid><description>The Dogecoin Foundation, established and led by members of the original core development team and long-time members of the Dogecoin community, has responsibility for providing governance and support for the Dogecoin cryptocurrency project.
Since 2014, the Foundation&amp;rsquo;s sole mission has been to protect and support the Dogecoin project, its reputation, and the global community of Shibes. The Foundation is committed to ensuring that Dogecoin continues to thrive, and can ultimately scale to being a widely used currency whilst simultaneously tackling changes at a pace that keeps-up with other cryptocurrencies.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The Dogecoin Foundation, established and led by members of the original core development team
and long-time members of the Dogecoin community, has responsibility for providing governance
and support for the Dogecoin cryptocurrency project.</p>
<p>Since 2014, the Foundation&rsquo;s sole mission has been to protect and support the Dogecoin project,
its reputation, and the global community of Shibes. The Foundation is committed to ensuring that
Dogecoin continues to thrive, and can ultimately scale to being a widely used currency whilst
simultaneously tackling changes at a pace that keeps-up with other cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>On January 23rd, 2022, three members of the Foundation, Michi Lumin, Ross Nicoll, and Tim Stebbing
will be participating in a video AMA (Ask-Me-Anything) with the community. The AMA will be live
streamed <a href="https://youtu.be/jctze9jZfTQ">here</a>. In anticipation of the AMA, a short update of recent Foundation
activities, all of which have been undertaken for the benefit of the Dogecoin community, includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Launching the first <a href="/trailmap/prologue/">Dogecoin Trailmap</a> to provide a vision for the future of the Dogecoin ecosystem.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Engaging with and consulting several potential commercial and non-commercial users of the GigaWallet project, gathering requirements and breaking ground on development.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Gathering a like-minded group of developers from the community interested in contributing to the Libdogecoin project and commencing development.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Establishing a team of community website and translation volunteers who are working diligently on the upcoming dogecoin.com website and the ‘Dogepedia’ in multiple languages.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>On-boarding long-term and previously unpaid volunteers in key functions, treating those individuals fairly and ensuring that the Dogecoin ecosystem can be resourced consistently in the future.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Establishing good governance and compliance principles, working with legal, accounting, and tax advisors to ensure proper use of any Foundation funds only for the benefit of the Dogecoin community.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Supporting and promoting the use of Dogecoin for important charitable causes, for example with <a href="https://dogecoin.com/teamseas/">#TeamSeas</a>, helping remove more than 30,000,000 pounds of trash from the oceans.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Started collaborating with non-profits that share Dogecoin’s spirit of playful discovery and learning such as <a href="https://hackclub.com/">Hack Club</a>.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Preventing hostile parties (including large corporates) from taking over or claiming ownership of Dogecoin through, e.g., bad faith trademark registrations; or to mislead the community by pretending to be Dogecoin or be affiliated with it. For example, please see our recent tweet <a href="https://twitter.com/DogecoinFdn/status/1484474892569305088?s=20">here</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Ensuring that the Dogecoin name, logo, and memes remain available for the community to use freely.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Liaising with the community, investors, technologists and other stakeholders around the world, to devise and implement opportunities for the cryptocurrency, to future-proof it for everyone.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Importantly, all of these actions have been taken to ensure that Dogecoin remains the People’s
cryptocurrency for years to come. The Foundation is dedicated, as always, to <strong>D</strong>oing <strong>O</strong>nly <strong>G</strong>ood <strong>E</strong>veryday.
The Foundation is currently putting together a note which will provide more detail regarding the Foundation’s
strategy, funding, and Tip Jar transactions. We look forward to sharing this information with you in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>You can read more about the Dogecoin Foundation, its members and its work at <a href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/">https://foundation.dogecoin.com/</a>.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>公告：狗狗幣基金會重組</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/announcements/2020-08-15-foundation-announcement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/zh-tw/announcements/2020-08-15-foundation-announcement/</guid><description>今天我們非常興奮地宣布狗狗幣基金會重組的消息 （原創立於 2014 年）。新的重點工作將放在對狗狗幣生態系和社群的支持，以及促進狗狗幣區塊鏈的未來發展。
焦點 狗狗幣核心錢包（Dogecoin Core Wallet） 目前仍是符合規範的狗狗幣錢包之首要參考實現（Reference implementation）。狗狗幣基金會的存在並不是為了「掌控」這個專案。我們的成立是為了加速開發工作，對目前狗狗幣核心專案以及未來的開發者們提供贊助，希望他們能全職投入，同時也歡迎想協助專案的新進貢獻者。
基金會也展望狗狗幣生態系在未來更加拓展、廣泛。幾周內我們將宣布一個向核心錢包致敬的新專案，它將對想要使用狗狗幣的金融、社交和慈善專案提供更容易使用的 API，以及更快速的整合方案。我們相信藉由全球的廣泛使用方能達成狗狗幣的成功，並將專注於能從根本提升狗狗幣採用率的基礎專案。
保護狗狗幣商標 多年以來，狗狗幣社群秉持對人們的信任，希望所有人都能自由使用狗狗幣的名稱和標誌。畢竟狗狗幣本是屬於人民的。
然而，近來有許多人企圖在多個國家與地區將狗狗幣商標納為私有，這可能使狗狗幣專案和社群無法繼續使用它。
這是個鮮為人知的故事，但我們想在此表揚社群中一隻非常棒的狗狗（Shibe）：Jens Wiechers，他從 2014 年起就代表狗狗幣基金會，透過專利商標事務所與這些惡意行為對抗，獨力作戰並獨自吸收了許多支出，捍衛每個人使用狗狗幣商標的權利。
基金會現擁有狗狗幣商標與品牌標誌，並將為社群維護它們。這代表基金會能繼續保護狗狗幣品牌，且允許人們（於非常自由的授權下）在相關的迷因、專案與各種有趣的事物上使用此商標 — 在這件事情上我們會挺你。
狗狗幣宣言 我們一直都在思考狗狗幣的意義：它是一個技術專案，同時也是一場帶給世界正向影響的運動。我們將它濃縮成四項聲明，並稱之為狗狗幣宣言。其中兩項專注於技術，另外兩項則與社群相關。
我們相信，這些體現「日日向善（Do Only Good Everyday）」的關鍵精神，會在我們制定決策、推進狗狗幣生態系發展時引領我們前進。
狗狗幣宣言
如果可以，請使用宣言頁面底部的推特連結簽署這份宣言。這將讓世界知道我們狗狗大軍（DogeArmy）代表的意義！
停一停、合作並傾聽！ 宣言的其中一項重要宗旨，是我們重視 合作與信任 更甚於 競爭與排外。秉持這樣的信念，我們建立了一個精實、非常睿智且令人讚嘆的顧問小組，成員來自數個不同領域，在我們尋求狗狗幣生態系的發展時更能相互支持。
看看我們令人驚豔的顧問團隊名單，請一定要為他們喝采，感謝他們付出的寶貴時間。
成功的代價 眾多志願者在過去幾個月裡孜孜不倦地努力，使基金會得以重建。然而我們也意識到，狗狗幣（在撰文當下，它是價值 440 億美元的金融產品）已經成長至數千人的企業那樣的規模。
許多人勤勉不懈地付出，使狗狗幣達到今日的成就，但他們同時也需要自己的正職工作，這讓他們相當疲憊，並且必須花費極大心力來應對狗狗幣受到的大量（好的與壞的）關注。
這造成的代價是：才華洋溢的新面孔們來到這裡希望對此專案提供協助，但沒人有餘力來歡迎他們，或幫他們找到貢獻的方式，於是他們受挫地離開了。文件的進度停滯、補丁尚未被檢閱，團隊人力有限，僅能將有限的時間優先用於處理重大問題。
贊助 我們相信狗狗幣專案值得一支能負擔這些繁重瑣碎任務的全職團隊，以幫助專案持續活躍下去。
基金會已正在準備預算，並且已經收到一些貢獻者的合作意向。我們計劃建立一個能負擔基金會行動支出以及開發成本的年度贊助商團隊。
我們的初始目標是確保有足夠三年的預算，使最低人手編制的人員可以全職地為狗狗幣專案貢獻，而不用擔心生計。
如果你願意支持狗狗幣基金會、有能力成為我們的主力贊助商，請與我們聯繫，我們很樂意與你聊聊。
滿滿的愛，
— 狗狗幣基金會</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>今天我們非常興奮地宣布<strong>狗狗幣基金會</strong>重組的消息 <em>（原創立於 2014 年）</em>。新的重點工作將放在對狗狗幣生態系和社群的支持，以及促進狗狗幣區塊鏈的未來發展。</p>
<h3 id="焦點">焦點</h3>
<p><em>狗狗幣核心錢包（Dogecoin Core Wallet）</em> 目前仍是符合規範的狗狗幣錢包之首要參考實現（Reference implementation）。狗狗幣基金會的存在並不是為了「掌控」這個專案。我們的成立是為了加速開發工作，對目前狗狗幣核心專案以及未來的開發者們提供贊助，希望他們能全職投入，同時也歡迎想協助專案的新進貢獻者。</p>
<p>基金會也展望狗狗幣生態系在未來更加拓展、廣泛。幾周內我們將宣布一個向核心錢包致敬的新專案，它將對想要使用狗狗幣的金融、社交和慈善專案提供更容易使用的 API，以及更快速的整合方案。我們相信藉由全球的廣泛使用方能達成狗狗幣的成功，並將專注於能從根本提升狗狗幣採用率的基礎專案。</p>
<h3 id="保護狗狗幣商標">保護狗狗幣商標</h3>
<p>多年以來，狗狗幣社群秉持對人們的信任，希望所有人都能自由使用狗狗幣的名稱和標誌。畢竟狗狗幣本是屬於人民的。</p>
<p>然而，近來有許多人企圖在多個國家與地區將狗狗幣商標納為私有，這可能使狗狗幣專案和社群無法繼續使用它。</p>
<p>這是個鮮為人知的故事，但我們想在此表揚社群中一隻非常棒的狗狗（Shibe）：Jens Wiechers，他從 2014 年起就代表狗狗幣基金會，透過專利商標事務所與這些惡意行為對抗，獨力作戰並獨自吸收了許多支出，捍衛每個人使用狗狗幣商標的權利。</p>
<p>基金會現擁有狗狗幣商標與品牌標誌，並將為社群維護它們。這代表基金會能繼續保護狗狗幣品牌，且允許人們（於非常自由的授權下）在相關的迷因、專案與各種有趣的事物上使用此商標 — 在這件事情上我們會挺你。</p>
<h3 id="狗狗幣宣言">狗狗幣宣言</h3>
<p>我們一直都在思考狗狗幣的意義：它是一個技術專案，同時也是一場帶給世界正向影響的運動。我們將它濃縮成四項聲明，並稱之為狗狗幣宣言。其中兩項專注於技術，另外兩項則與社群相關。</p>
<p>我們相信，這些體現「日日向善（Do Only Good Everyday）」的關鍵精神，會在我們制定決策、推進狗狗幣生態系發展時引領我們前進。</p>
<p><a href="/zh-tw/manifesto">狗狗幣宣言</a></p>
<p>如果可以，請使用宣言頁面底部的推特連結簽署這份宣言。這將讓世界知道我們狗狗大軍（DogeArmy）代表的意義！</p>
<h3 id="停一停合作並傾聽">停一停、合作並傾聽！</h3>
<p>宣言的其中一項重要宗旨，是我們重視 <em>合作與信任</em> 更甚於 <em>競爭與排外</em>。秉持這樣的信念，我們建立了一個精實、非常睿智且令人讚嘆的顧問小組，成員來自數個不同領域，在我們尋求狗狗幣生態系的發展時更能相互支持。</p>
<p><a href="/zh-tw/about">看看我們令人驚豔的顧問團隊名單</a>，請一定要為他們喝采，感謝他們付出的寶貴時間。</p>
<h3 id="成功的代價">成功的代價</h3>
<p>眾多志願者在過去幾個月裡孜孜不倦地努力，使基金會得以重建。然而我們也意識到，狗狗幣（在撰文當下，它是價值 440 億美元的金融產品）已經成長至數千人的企業那樣的規模。</p>
<p>許多人勤勉不懈地付出，使狗狗幣達到今日的成就，但他們同時也需要自己的正職工作，這讓他們相當疲憊，並且必須花費極大心力來應對狗狗幣受到的大量（好的與壞的）關注。</p>
<p>這造成的代價是：才華洋溢的新面孔們來到這裡希望對此專案提供協助，但沒人有餘力來歡迎他們，或幫他們找到貢獻的方式，於是他們受挫地離開了。文件的進度停滯、補丁尚未被檢閱，團隊人力有限，僅能將有限的時間優先用於處理重大問題。</p>
<h3 id="贊助">贊助</h3>
<p>我們相信狗狗幣專案值得一支能負擔這些繁重瑣碎任務的全職團隊，以幫助專案持續活躍下去。</p>
<p>基金會已正在準備預算，並且已經收到一些貢獻者的合作意向。我們計劃建立一個能負擔基金會行動支出以及開發成本的年度贊助商團隊。</p>
<p>我們的初始目標是確保有足夠三年的預算，使最低人手編制的人員可以全職地為狗狗幣專案貢獻，而不用擔心生計。</p>
<p>如果你願意支持狗狗幣基金會、有能力成為我們的主力贊助商，請與我們聯繫，我們很樂意與你聊聊。</p>
<p></br></br>
滿滿的愛，<br>
— 狗狗幣基金會
</br></br></p>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>