<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advisories on Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/</link><description>Recent content in Advisories on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advisory: Response to transactions being automatically retried</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/2021-11-11-transaction-broadcast/</guid><description>Note: A previous version of this advisory used &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; to refer to a group separate to the Foundation. It has been edited to clarify.
Binance has today paused Dogecoin withdrawals and stated they have found a &amp;ldquo;minor issue&amp;rdquo; in Dogecoin. The Foundation wishes to address this:
Several months ago (noting while an earlier post stated a year, first confirmed mention is April) Binance notified a group of Dogecoin Core maintainers that Binance had cases where transactions were stuck, meaning the transactions were not being mined successfully.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Note: A previous version of this advisory used &ldquo;we&rdquo; to refer to a group separate to the Foundation. It has been edited to
clarify.</p>
<p>Binance has today paused Dogecoin withdrawals and stated they have found a &ldquo;minor issue&rdquo; in Dogecoin. The Foundation wishes to address this:</p>
<p>Several months ago (noting while an earlier post stated a year, first confirmed mention is April) Binance notified a group of Dogecoin Core maintainers that Binance had cases where transactions were stuck, meaning the transactions were not being mined successfully. The maintainers suggested Binance use RBF (replace by fee) on these transactions, which would replace the original transactions with a new transaction with a higher fee paid. Notably this was suggested because replace by fee invalidates the previous transaction (hence &ldquo;replace&rdquo;). As the transaction had RBF disabled, it was recommended that Binance create a new transaction manually, which would consume the same inputs to forcibly invalidate the previous transaction.</p>
<p>Some time later Binance notified the maintainers that they had account reconciliation issues. The maintainers were unable to reproduce those issues with the data we were given by Binance, but at the time suggested using the <code>-zapwallettxes</code> command line option to mitigate the issue. This is notable as it is anticipated this would have also prevented the issue seen.</p>
<p>Yesterday November 10th Binance notified the maintainers that previously stuck transactions had suddenly relayed successfully, post 1.14.5 update; likely because minfees have been lowered in 1.14.5, making the previously valid but unrelayable transactions relayable. The sole example provided is a transaction with fees which are valid as of v1.14.5, but were invalid (too low) in 1.14.3 and before. Note, Binance updated directly from v1.14.3 to 1.14.5, in the past few days.</p>
<p>Based on the information available it appears that the previously stuck transactions have been retried automatically, as would happen on each node restart after upgrade - and went through, since now the minimum required relay fee is lower. This is correct behaviour as a result of reducing fees.</p>
<h2 id="lessons">Lessons</h2>
<ul>
<li>Correct handling to cancel a transaction is to spend the to-be-cancelled transaction&rsquo;s inputs to a different transaction, which invalidates the first.
<ul>
<li>Ideally use replace-by-fee if available, but otherwise crafting and sending a transaction spending the previously chosen inputs, will invalidate the previous transaction.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Please note that transactions don&rsquo;t have a defined timeout period, but are typically discarded due to memory limits.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="guidance">Guidance</h2>
<p>The Foundation has received no further reports of this happening. For any providers with concerns about stagnant invalid transactions, we recommend stopping the nodes, removing the mempool.dat file just in case, and then starting the node with <code>-zapwallettxes</code>.</p>
<p>For individual users with concerns, note that sending all of your Dogecoins back to yourself (ideally a new address, but you can use an existing one for this) will also spend any previous transaction outputs, and invalidate any such &ldquo;stuck&rdquo; transactions.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>Conselho: Comunicado em relação ao projeto cripto 'Dogecoin 2.0'</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/2021-08-31-advisory-dogecoin2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/2021-08-31-advisory-dogecoin2/</guid><description>Alguns Shibes preocupados da comunidade Dogecoin recentemente trouxeram à nossa atenção o projeto cripto &amp;lsquo;Dogecoin 2.0&amp;rsquo;, que começou no início deste ano e acabou de anunciar que vai ser listado em exchanges de renome.
Como de costume, a Fundação Dogecoin dá as boas vindas aos recém-chegados ao espaço cripto, mas este projeto não tem nenhuma ligação ou conexão com Dogecoin. Para proteger a comunidade Dogecoin de ser induzida em erro e para proteger o nome da Dogecoin de ser usado indevidamente, nós pedimos aos nossos advogados de proteção de marca para contatar os criadores do produto &amp;lsquo;Dogecoin 2.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Alguns Shibes preocupados da comunidade Dogecoin recentemente trouxeram à nossa atenção o projeto cripto &lsquo;Dogecoin 2.0&rsquo;, que começou no início deste ano e acabou de anunciar que vai ser listado em exchanges de renome.</p>
<p>Como de costume, a Fundação Dogecoin dá as boas vindas aos recém-chegados ao espaço cripto, mas este projeto não tem nenhuma ligação ou conexão com Dogecoin. Para proteger a comunidade Dogecoin de ser induzida em erro e para proteger o nome da Dogecoin de ser usado indevidamente, nós pedimos aos nossos advogados de proteção de marca para contatar os criadores do produto &lsquo;Dogecoin 2.0&rsquo; .</p>
<p>Nós temos esperança que o nosso pedido razoável vá fazer com que a equipa de desenvolvimento deles escolha um nome novo para o seu projeto que não infrinja os direitos e reputação do projeto Dogecoin, e ansiamos ver as inovações que eles possam trazer com os seus futuros empreendimentos.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>Claims of Affiliation with Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/2020-08-18-not-affiliated-moonrabbit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/advisories/2020-08-18-not-affiliated-moonrabbit/</guid><description>Neither the Dogecoin project, the Dogecoin Foundation or any affiliated developers or entities have partnered with MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu or any affiliated entities, including the purported Dogecoin Foundation using the domain doge.org. This purported organisation and domain are, as far as we have been able to ascertain, run by the same people who run MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu.
As such, any claim of &amp;ldquo;partnering up&amp;rdquo; appears to be designed to create a false appearance of partnership and association with the long-established Dogecoin project and Dogecoin Foundation.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Neither the Dogecoin project, the Dogecoin Foundation or any affiliated developers or entities have partnered with MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu or any affiliated entities, including the purported Dogecoin Foundation using the domain doge.org. This purported organisation and domain are, as far as we have been able to ascertain, run by the same people who run MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu.</p>
<p>As such, any claim of &ldquo;partnering up&rdquo; appears to be designed to create a false appearance of partnership and association with the long-established Dogecoin project and Dogecoin Foundation.</p>
<p>We should also note that the MoonRabbit AngoZaibatsu corporation is actively attempting to register a trademark for the &ldquo;Dogecoin&rdquo; name in both Europe as well as the United States. The Dogecoin Project and the Dogecoin Foundation are actively in the process of opposing these and other bad faith attempts to register such trademarks on the grounds that those entities have no connection to Dogecoin and are attempting to profit unfairly off of the goodwill Dogecoin has built over the last eight years since its inception.</p>
<p>Please be assured that we are making all necessary investigations to ascertain the facts in this rapidly evolving matter. For the avoidance of doubt, enquires should be directed to members of the Dogecoin Project, the Dogecoin Core developers, and the Dogecoin Foundation only through channels listed on either <a href="https://dogecoin.com/">dogecoin.com</a> or <a href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/">foundation.dogecoin.com</a> and not through any other email, social media acccount or website purported to be affiliated with Dogecoin.</p>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>