<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Trailmaps on Dogecoin Foundation</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/trailmap/</link><description>Recent content in Trailmaps on Dogecoin Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/trailmap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/trailmap/prologue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/trailmap/prologue/</guid><description>Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp;amp; Dogepedia Project: Libdogecoin Project: Dogecoin Standard Project: GigaWallet Project: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) Project: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) Proposal: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) Partnership: Point of Sale (L2 app) What is the Dogecoin Trailmap? While roadmap is a term that&amp;rsquo;s commonly used when new cryptocurrencies are released, it conveys a rigid way forward, led by a single company or &amp;rsquo;lead&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>Project: Dogecoin Standard</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/trailmap/standard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/trailmap/standard/</guid><description>Project: Dogecoin Standard Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp;amp; Dogepedia Project: Libdogecoin Project: Dogecoin Standard Project: GigaWallet Project: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) Project: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) Proposal: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) Partnership: Point of Sale (L2 app) Dogecoin Standard - A Specification. The Dogecoin Standard will be a Written Specification and validating test suite derived from the Dogecoin Core Wallet during the process of creating libdogecoin.</description></item><item><title>Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp; Dogepedia</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/trailmap/website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/trailmap/website/</guid><description>Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp;amp; Dogepedia Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp;amp; Dogepedia Project: Libdogecoin Project: Dogecoin Standard Project: GigaWallet Project: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) Project: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) Proposal: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) Partnership: Point of Sale (L2 app) Dogecoin.com makeover. Volunteers from the Doge Army have come together from all over the world to work on a re-design of the Dogecoin.</description></item><item><title>Project: GigaWallet</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/trailmap/gigawallet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/trailmap/gigawallet/</guid><description>Project: GigaWallet Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp;amp; Dogepedia Project: Libdogecoin Project: Dogecoin Standard Project: GigaWallet Project: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) Project: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) Proposal: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) Partnership: Point of Sale (L2 app) GigaWallet, an enterprise-ready dogecoin service for your platform. As we&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned in the Prologue, we believe that utility comes from adoption and adoption comes from utility, it&amp;rsquo;s a feedback loop that is on the slow path right now due to friction around platform adoption.</description></item><item><title>Project: Libdogecoin</title><link>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/trailmap/libdogecoin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foundation.dogecoin.com/pt/trailmap/libdogecoin/</guid><description>Project: Libdogecoin Dogecoin Trailmap: Prologue Project: Dogecoin.com makeover &amp;amp; Dogepedia Project: Libdogecoin Project: Dogecoin Standard Project: GigaWallet Project: Dogecoin Keyring (App / SDK) Project: RadioDoge (Starlink + Radio nodes for remote locations) Proposal: Community Staking (Proof of Stake) Partnership: Point of Sale (L2 app) Libdogecoin, a clean C library of Dogecoin building blocks. Libdogecoin will be a complete implementation of the Dogecoin Protocols, as a C library (and series of bindings to popular languages) which will allow anyone to build a Dogecoin compliant product, without needing to worry about the deeper specifics of the crypto functions.</description></item></channel></rss>